Search for:  Search Button

Search for:Search Button

Everything About Amazon Fire TV Stick

    Search for:Search Button

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the **“**[Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)” website collects, uses, maintains and discloses its user information. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to assist you in understanding the purpose for which we collect, use, disclose and process the personal data you have provided to us or we collect in accordance with the applicable international Data Protection laws.

By interacting or submitting any personal data or any other information to “[Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)**”** for any events, it’s deemed to be your full consent to permit us to collect, use and disclose such Personal Data and other information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use www.firesticktricks.com. We reserve the right to update or make changes to this Privacy Policy. If we update or make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will post the change in this Privacy Policy. Your continuing use of the website will be deemed to be your acceptance of these changes.

The use of any terms such as, “We”, “Our”, “Us” “it’s” etc., in this “Privacy Policy” will be deemed to be the representation of “[Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)”. Also use of any term such as, “You”, “Your”, “They”, “Their” etc. will deem to be the representation of users of the [www.firesticktricks.com](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)

### **Collection of Personal Data:**

We the “[Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)” collect personal information including but not limited to Name and email address etc. from our users. We may obtain your Data when you provide it to us by subscribing to our newsletter and

* We may collect your Data in the ordinary course of our relationship with you.
* We may collect Personal Data that you manifestly choose to make public, including via our Site.
* We may collect or obtain Personal Data when you visit our Site, or use any features or resources available on or through our Site. When you visit our Site, your device and browser will automatically disclose certain information, some of which may constitute Personal Data.

We may also collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. The non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and other similar information. We do not seek to collect or otherwise Process your Sensitive Personal Data.

### Web browser cookies:

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

We use a session cookie on our site to determine whether or not you are accepting cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser to prevent that. Here are the instructions to control cookies on your browser – http://www.aboutcookies.org.uk/managing-cookies

### How we use collected information:

“**Fire Stick Tricks**” may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

* To personify the user experience.
* To maintain your interest with us.
* Respond to your inquiries.
* To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
* Comply with all applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies, including reasonable necessity to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders.

“**Fire Stick Tricks”** does not share any of your personally identifiable or transactional information with any person or entity, other than as set out in this policy. No other third party receives your personally identifiable information or other transactional data and In no circumstances **“Fire Stick Tricks”** do not rent, sell, or share it’s user’s Personal with other people or non-affiliated companies for marketing without your permission.

### **Information We May Disclose:**

In the following circumstances, we may disclose your information

* With your prior permission.
* By the application of law within or outside your territory, legal process, litigation requests.
* By requesting from any governmental authorities.
* To protect our legal rights, liabilities, and interests.

**“**[Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)” has sole discretion to take all reasonable steps to secure the information against unauthorized access or disclosure.  In no event, we do not sell trade, rent or otherwise transfer your identifiable information to any third parties except the above circumstances.

### **Sharing your Personal Information:**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third-party service providers to help us operate our website or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### **Your Choices:**

You may, of course, decline to submit information through the “[Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)” Platform, in which case we may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may also control the types of notifications and communications we send, limit the information shared within the “[Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)” Platform about you, and otherwise amend certain privacy settings.

### How we protect your information:

We take all reasonable and necessary steps to protect the information provided by you from unauthorized access. We follow commonly accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us. We are also using the SSL CERTIFICATE security system for ensuring and protect the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% safe and secure. Therefore, we are not in the actual position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

### **Content Privacy Policy:**

You own your content. We don’t. All your content belongs to you. We don’t share your content and we don’t spy on you or your content. Illegal activity is not permitted. If we are made aware of illegal activity, we will take appropriate action. We ask that you not post any unlawful, harmful, obscene, or pornographic content. Please see our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.firesticktricks.com/terms-of-service) for the list of activities that are not permitted at “[Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)”

### **Tracking Privacy Policy:**

We don’t track you personally and we never sell your personal data. Here is what we track: we track how users use our site in general so that we can make it better. We are monitoring traffic, usage activity, site performance, and we use general analytic tools so that we can improve your experience. We do not associate any of this data with you personally. We never sell or share your personally identifiable information unless required to do so by law.

### Electronic newsletters:

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. We may use third-party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### Third-party websites:

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Advertising:

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Google Adsense:

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy\_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

### Google Signals Data Collection:

Our website utilizes Google Analytics and Google Ads, which includes the use of Google Signals. This section of our Privacy Policy is dedicated to explaining how we collect, use, and protect data in conjunction with Google Signals.

#### What is Google Signals?

Google Signals is a feature within Google Analytics that allows us to collect additional information about users who have turned on Ads Personalization in their Google account settings. This feature enhances our understanding of our audience and helps us to deliver more relevant and personalized advertising experiences.

#### Data Collection and Use

1. **Types of Data Collected**: When you visit our website, Google Signals may collect data such as your device type, browser information, and interactions with our website and ads. This may include demographic and interest data if you have Ads Personalization enabled.
2. **Purpose of Data Collection**: The data collected through Google Signals is used to:
    * Understand and analyze website traffic and user behavior.
    * Create more effective marketing campaigns.
    * Provide personalized ad experiences across devices.
    * Measure the performance of our ads and website.
3. **Cross-Device Tracking**: Google Signals enables cross-device tracking when you are signed into your Google account. This means that we may understand how you interact with our content across multiple devices, helping us to optimize our website and ads accordingly.

#### Managing Your Data

1. **Accessing Your Data**: You can view and manage your data associated with Google Signals through [Google’s “My Activity” feature](https://myactivity.google.com/). This tool allows you to see a summary of your data collected by Google services, including data used for personalizing ads.
2. **Deleting Your Data**: If you wish to delete your Google Signals data, you can do so through the “[My Activity](https://myactivity.google.com/)” feature. Here, you have the option to delete specific activities or entire topics based on your preferences.
3. **Opt-Out Options**: You have control over your data. You can opt out of Ads Personalization through your Google account settings. Additionally, you can use Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs for the web.

#### Data Protection and Privacy

1. **Anonymity and Aggregation**: The data collected through Google Signals is anonymized and aggregated. We do not have access to personally identifiable information unless explicitly provided by you through other means (e.g., signing up for a newsletter).
2. **Data Sharing and Security**: We do not share Google Signals data with third parties in a way that would reveal your personal identity. We implement robust security measures to protect the data from unauthorized access or breaches.

#### Compliance and Cooperation

We comply with all applicable laws and regulations regarding data protection and privacy. We also adhere to Google’s policies and guidelines for the use of Google Signals.

### Compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### **Governing Law and Jurisdiction:**

We do our best to protect your identity at all times and we are respectful of the law. **“**[Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)” will disclose personally-identifying information when required to do so by law. This Privacy Policy and its interpretation and operation are governed solely by all Data Privacy, GDPR or Data protection Law applicable in the territory of the users. We and each user may submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the local territory of the users.

### Changes to this privacy policy

“**Fire Stick Tricks**” has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### **Questionnaires and To Contact us:**

**“Fire Stick Tricks”** have sole jurisdiction to provide the explanation of this “Privacy Policy”. Feel free if you have any questions regarding this “Privacy Policy”. To contact us, use the following links below:

**Website**: [https://www.firesticktricks.com](https://www.firesticktricks.com/)

**Contact Form:** [https://www.firesticktricks.com/contact](https://www.firesticktricks.com/contact)

_FYI:_ _Please note that the content of this page can be changed without any prior notice._

_This Privacy Policy was last updated on Sunday, January 21, 2024._

Search this website

Top VPNs
--------

|     |
| --- |
| Our #1 Pick<br><br>[<br><br>](https://www.firesticktricks.com/recommends/expressvpn-firestick3)<br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>30-day money-back guarantee<br><br>[Visit ExpressVPN](https://www.firesticktricks.com/recommends/expressvpn-firestick4)<br><br>[Read review](https://www.firesticktricks.com/expressvpn-review.html) |
| [<br><br>](https://www.firesticktricks.com/recommends/ipvanish-firestick)<br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>30-day money-back guarantee<br><br>[Visit IPVanish](https://www.firesticktricks.com/recommends/ipvanish-firestick) |
| [<br><br>](https://www.firesticktricks.com/recommends/pia-organic-deal)<br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>30-day money-back guarantee<br><br>[Visit PIA](https://www.firesticktricks.com/recommends/pia-organic-deal) |

#### Trending Guides

1. [Best VPN for FireStick](https://www.firesticktricks.com/install-best-vpn-firestick.html)
2. [How to Jailbreak a FireStick](https://www.firesticktricks.com/jailbreak-fire-stick.html)
3. [How to Install Kodi on FireStick](https://www.firesticktricks.com/install-kodi-on-firestick.html)
4. [Best Kodi Addons](https://www.firesticktricks.com/best-kodi-addons.html)
5. [Best Kodi Builds](https://www.firesticktricks.com/best-kodi-builds.html)
6. [Best FireStick Apps](https://www.firesticktricks.com/amazon-fire-stick-apps.html)
7. [IPTV](https://www.firesticktricks.com/best-iptv-service.html)
8. [Cinema APK](https://www.firesticktricks.com/cinema-apk-firestick.html)
9. [Free Movie Streaming Sites](https://www.firesticktricks.com/free-movie-streaming-sites.html)
10. [Best Torrent Sites](https://www.firesticktricks.com/torrent-sites.html)
11. [Free Sports Streaming Sites](https://www.firesticktricks.com/free-sports-streaming-sites.html)

#### Recent Posts

* [How to Watch WWE King and Queen of the Ring on FireStick (Cody Rhodes vs. Logan Paul)](https://www.firesticktricks.com/watch-wwe-king-and-queen-of-the-ring-on-firestick.html)
* [Why Does My FireStick Keep Buffering? (How to Fix Common Issues)](https://www.firesticktricks.com/fix-firestick-buffering.html)
* [How to Watch FA Cup Final on FireStick (Man City vs. Man United)](https://www.firesticktricks.com/watch-fa-cup-final-on-firestick.html)
* [How to Jailbreak FireStick \[New Secrets Unlocked in May 2024\]](https://www.firesticktricks.com/jailbreak-fire-stick.html)

[

](https://www.firesticktricks.com/ "Fire Stick Tricks")[

](https://www.dmca.com/Protection/Status.aspx?ID=3d1d3e26-a89f-4db5-929b-a621ff26c548 "DMCA.com Protection Status")

© Copyright 2024 [Fire Stick Tricks](https://www.firesticktricks.com/) · All Rights Reserved

Disclaimer – Streaming or downloading copyright content is unlawful.

FireStickTricks.com do not in any way condone, promote or encourage any illegal use of Kodi, Fire Stick or our guides. Users are responsible for their actions. [Read our full disclaimer](https://www.firesticktricks.com/disclaimer).

🔥 [Try ExpressVPN Risk-Free (3 Months Free)](https://www.firesticktricks.com/recommends/expressvpn-sticky2)

X
